The guests have all checked out.
Ready for your inspection.
Good.
Happy New Year.
I'll report back next year.
There are still many days until the New Year.
Why are you closing
so early?
Bosses need holidays too.
Let's talk about it next year.
Should we start buying tickets
to go home early for the New Year?
Mr. Tang and I
are locals.
We will be staying in Nan'an.
Who are you calling "we"?
Xinyue and I will stay here too.
Please take me in.
I don't want to go back and be pushed into marriage.
What about you, Mr. Zhang?
I'm fine with whatever.
Whatever?
I can be anywhere.
It's always been like this.
Just stay.
There are exactly six of us. Everything goes smoothly.
They are closing the homestay.
Tell me,
should I close or not?
Whatever.
We are quite busy before the New Year.
The company has a lot of procedures.
The offer letter might only be issued to you
after you report to duty after the New Year.
Please understand.
Okay, no problem.
Thanks for your hard work.
You're welcome.
Three years ago,
I actually met her.
How could there be such a coincidence in the world?
The delivery for this floor is at the door.
Okay.
What a coincidence.
You also ordered this super delicious food.
I mean,
bumping into each other at this exact time
is quite a coincidence.
People all over the world probably eat at this hour.
What about workaholics
and people who stay up late playing games?
You win.
I'm not trying to win.
I...
I mean,
Xinyue.
Zhang Yang.
Come down after eating.
I need you for something.
Here comes the real workaholic.
This is nice. Look.
This is fun.
Yeah.
What about this one?
This one looks good. What do you think?
Have you been here before?
No.
When did you do all this?
When you two were being homebodies.
Since the New Year is almost here,
tonight,
we are going to have a very cool dinner party.
Guess who's going grocery shopping.
Me?
I've sent you the list.
Don't forget anything.
Why me?
You guys weren't around when we were cleaning up earlier.
I'll wash the dishes.
Then I'll take out the trash.
I'll take out the trash.
I'll walk everyone back.
Then I'll prep the ingredients we bought.
I'll prepare 1 pot of tea,
5 appetizers,
10 main courses,
2 desserts,
and 1 fruit platter.
I'll call everyone out to eat when it's ready.
This is good.
I will prepare the ingredients we bought,
and make a cup of tea,
5 appetizers,
10 main courses,
2 desserts,
plus a fruit platter.
I will call everyone out to eat when it's done.
This is good.
Go ahead and buy carefully.
Look at this.
This is good.
I think this is nice.
Sure.
Let me help you carry some.
No need.
Putting so much stuff in one bag,
doesn't it hurt your hand?
Plastic bags are 50 cents each.
So expensive.
You're such a cheapskate.
Just give me
the small one.
No need, no need, no need.
Tell me.
Do you think we're incompatible?
Things like this happen every time we go to the supermarket.
Then we must be very compatible.
Let's go.
Tea: Drink Water and Think of the Source.
Appetizer: Colorful Life.
Main course: Midnight Light,
Eastward Expedition Across the Sea.
There are a few more dishes with names too long to remember.
And these two desserts,
Same Roots and Origins,
Family Reunion.
This is the Chenggong Family Banquet.
How is it?
Amazing.
Um,
what is the Chenggong Family Banquet?
The Chenggong Family Banquet
is a local specialty banquet created
to pay tribute to Zheng Chenggong.
It's a national delicacy.
A famous listed banquet.
So there are stories hidden in these dish names.
Of course.
Tell me what you think.
This is great.
You have these cooking skills?
Did they buy you seasoning packets?
These
were all made by Mr. Zhang.
I'm just helping out.
Pardon my poor skills.
What are you pretending for?
Showing off like a peacock.
Alright, alright.
Since everyone is here,
let's sit down and start the meal.
Come on.
Okay.
Well then...
I'd like to propose a toast.
I'm very happy to have met you all this year.
In the future, no matter where you are
or what you do, may things get better and better.
Our slogan is,
Come to Nan'an, you will succeed!
Cheers.
Happy New Year.
Are you
not going home for the New Year?
It's fine as long as my brother is there.
You have a brother?
He is nothing like me.
He's an executive in a big company.
He's smart,
handsome,
and my parents like him more.
Unlike me,
who just fools around.
That's called slowing down and enjoying life.
Life is about
finding a balance.
Congratulations.
You've graduated.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
You're welcome.
But
I should thank you too.
Joining the travel agency
gave me a new goal.
Heading in one direction
and pushing forward feels pretty good.
Then
congratulations on your graduation too.
Then I must thank you again.
Nan'an is really beautiful.
You still remember what I said.
Of course.
I have a great memory.
Li Xinyue.
Five.
Four.
I like you.
I...
No.
Don't be nervous.
I...
I didn't mean that.
Didn't we agree he'd set off the fireworks right on time?
I just wanted to do it then,
with a bang.
Then I'd whisper it.
You could pretend you didn't hear it,
and we'd act like it never happened.
Don't feel burdened.
I don't need you to do anything.
I just wanted to tell you tactfully.
By the way,
did you know?
We actually met a long time ago.
A few days ago,
I was looking through the photos on my phone.
I found out that three years ago,
when I went out of town for a shoot,
I actually took a picture of you.
I'm sorry.
It's fine, Weld.
I know.
You don't want to stay here.
As if
you'd be willing to be with me long-distance.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.